good morning.
お は ようございます
I really have a friend today.
今日、本当に友達がいるんだけど
Hello, nice to meet you.
どうも、初めまして
Isn't something like this good?
こういうのもいいでしょ?
Someone can see it.
誰かが見られるっていう
It's a little embarrassing though.
ちょっと恥ずかしいけど
It's fresh.
新鮮で
Is it fresh?
新鮮で?
There's no one to match, right?
誰か見合えることないでしょ?
My home.
自分の家って
Have you ever had any unusual sex?
変わったエッチとかしたことある?
Until now.
今まで
Unusual sex?
変わったエッチ?
In the car.
車の中で
picture?
え?
By car?
車で?
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
ちょっとね
I've only done it properly.
ちゃんとだけしたことあるけど
What is car sex?
カーセックスってやつ?
Where is it?
どこだよ?
parking?
駐車場?
That's right.
だ よね
There aren't any humans, I guess.
人系のいないよ、なんか
How do you fix car depression?
車のうつはどうやってやるの?
Ingenious seats.
工夫座席に
Go.
行って
Defeat it.
倒して
All sheets and stuff.
全部シートとか
Defeat it.
倒して
Are you excited?
興奮は?
I did, I was excited.
しました、興奮
Just a little bit.
ちょっとね
The thrill.
スリルが
An empty parking lot in the countryside.
誰もいない、田舎の駐車場とか
Is there no one?
誰 もいない?
Rural parking lot.
田舎の駐車場
It's a little dangerous in the city.
都内はちょっと危ないね
Next time, in Tokyo
今度、都内でや
Ru.
る
In the morning, the grass is real.
朝 草がほんとやねん
Have you gone anywhere recently?
最近、どこか遊びに行ったりした?
I went to Asakusa with my friend.
友達と一緒に朝草に行きました
Morning grass?
朝草?
what have you been up to?
何してたの?
Eating out and going to war.
食べ歩きをして、 戦争をして
nice.
いいね
So, have sex.
で、セックスして
It's a little different.
ちょっと違うね
But it flew away.
飛んじゃったんだけど
Have sex in war.
戦争でセックスをして
What aren't you doing?
何してない?
I'd like to have sex in a horse-drawn carriage.
馬車でセックスとか してみたいよね
He didn't say he'd ever had sex in a carriage.
馬車でセックスしたことあるって 言ってませんでした
He's a pervert.
変態なんですよ
he.
彼は
amazing.
すごい
He's a pervert.
変態なんですよ
he.
彼は
Really.
本当に
I want to hear it.
聞きたい
Lots of stories.
話いっぱい
There are quite a few.
結構ありますよ
I want to hear it.
聞きたい
Please do that next time.
それ今度にしてね
I can't stand the sight of these feet anymore.
俺はもうこの足がすると もうたまらなくて
Hey, I can only tell you about my previous bare legs.
ねえ、以前の生足しか 言えないからさ
Have you come back?
帰ってきてくれた?
From home?
お家から?
It smells like sweat.
汗まんだ匂いが
I hate it, I hate it, I hate it.
嫌だ嫌だ嫌だ
It's annoying so no.
うざいからダメダメ
Embarrassing, embarrassing.
恥ずかしい恥ずかしい
vanilla.
バニラ
It tastes like vanilla.
バニラの味をするよ
Really a lie.
本当に嘘
TRUE.
本当
Have you ever played with your feet?
足でいじってことないの?
No, no, no.
ないないない
Looks like I'll be leaving soon.
もうちょっと 行っちゃいそうだよ
Is it a little early?
ちょっと早い?
With both feet.
両足で
両 足で
Hanchira.
ハンチラが
難
Yes.
しい
I don't like it, I don't like it.
嫌 だ嫌だ
why?
なんで?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
I still have to stalk this.
まだこれストーキングをしないと
That's kind of amazing.
あれ、なんかすごい
The corbel.
ハンチがさ
It's T.
Tじゃん
I don't like it.
嫌だ
T
Did you come like this?
こんないっちゃうの来てくれたの?
Take a look at the camera.
ちょっとカメラ見てごらん
It's looking amazing right now.
今すごい見られてる
I don't like it.
嫌だ
This is my own thing.
これ自前のやつだよね
I could see it.
見えちゃった
I can see it, I can see it.
見えちゃう見えちゃう
amazing.
すごい
It doesn't make any sense.
意味ないよ
It's still working.
まだ機能してるよ
It's so scary.
めっちゃ怖い
I could see it.
見えちゃった
I have no choice but to go home.
帰るしかないね
I'm getting wet.
濡れちゃう
It's hot, isn't it?
暑いでしょ
Is it getting hot?
暑くなってきた?
My body is hot.
体ほてって
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Slowly and steadily.
ゆっくりじゅーっと
Ah, amazing.
あ、すごい
I can't see it at all.
まる見えない
I don't like it, I don't like it.
嫌だ嫌だ
Do your nails slowly.
ネイルをゆっくり
Here.
ここ ね
superior.
上
I'll look closely.
しっかり見るから
I don't like it, I don't like it.
嫌だ嫌だ
You don't have to see it.
見なくていい
I'll close my eyes.
目つぶっとくわ
It's open.
開いてる
開 いてる
close.
近い
close?
近い?
It's been a while.
久しぶりだね
I'm giving out the weight.
重さ出してます
What are you hiding?
何を隠すの?
The soup is beautiful.
スープは綺麗
I don't have tights.
タイツがない
What should I do?
どうしよう?
It feels half-hearted.
中途半端な感じ
It's erotic.
エロいよ
delicious?
おいしい?
I'm going to go ahead.
ゆくゆくしちゃう
Will it go away?
ゆくゆくしちゃう?
Normally like this.
普通にこう
It's smooth.
さらさらだね
It was too light to see.
さらさらすぎて見えなかった
Do it again.
もう一回やって
Looks delicious.
おいしそう
I don't like it.
嫌だ
I'll take it home.
持って帰るね
It's just barely.
ギリギリだね
I can see the meat.
肉が見えてる
Meat eating.
肉食い込み
The meat.
肉が
Fully visible.
丸見え
I don't like it.
嫌だ
You don't have to see it.
見なくていい
So smooth.
すっごいスルスル
I can't see it.
見えない
It became soggy.
ブシャブシャになっちゃった
I lost my eyesight.
目が見えなくなっちゃったね
It's no good to leave right away.
すぐ行っちゃうのがダメだよ
It's really big.
すごい大きい
What should I do?
どうしよう?
どうしようかね
Will you lick that part?
そんなとこ舐めてくれるの?
You've grown.
成長したね
Just with your mouth.
口やだけでね
That's amazing.
すごいね
すごいよ
copper?
どう?
That's amazing though.
すごいんだけど
Does it feel good?
気 持ちいい?
Yeah.
うん
It's got great sound.
すごい 音が入るね
It's a small one.
ちっちゃいのがね
Feels good.
気持ちいい
together...
一緒に...
Let's go to America together.
一緒にアメリカでしょ
amazing.
すごい
It's completely visible.
丸見えだよ
I don't like it.
嫌だ
嫌 だよ
You don't have to see it.
見なくていい
Isn't it just to look?
見るだけじゃないのか
I don't like it.
嫌だ
I want you to include it.
入れてほしい
What?
何を?
I want Zhen Chen included.
ジェンチェン入れてほしい
Zhenchen?
ジ ェンチェン?
I can see it.
見えちゃうよ
I'll just put it in like this.
このまま入れちゃうよ
This is what's going on here.
ここ までこれが入ってくるんだよ
amazing.
すごい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
That's amazing.
すごいね
Very powerful.
すごい力強い
feeling
気持ち
good.
いい
Yeah.
うん
You're really good at it.
すごい 上手だよ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
feeling
気持
Good.
ち いい
I also wear it on my body.
体にもかいてる
That's amazing.
すごいよ
Well done.
えっとり
Try touching it.
触ってみて
The one that's out.
出てるやつ
Make it muddy.
ドロドロして
I have to wash it off once.
一旦、洗い流さないとね
what up?
どうした?
picture?
え?
Is it you?
あなただ?
Yeah.
うん
Should you go?
あなた行こうかな
You're coming.
あなた来るよ
picture?
え?
what?
何?
Did you want to read it?
読めたかった?
Why why why?
なんでなんでなんで?
You got on the phone, right?
電話に乗ったでしょ?
why?
なんで?
Sorry about this.
これで、ごめんなさい
Make this place.
ここを作る
copper?
どう?
Yeah.
うん
I'm hungry.
お腹が空いた
Your soup is empty.
あなたのスープが空いた
I'm hungry.
お腹が空いた
This is what happened.
こう なってきた
Why why?
なんでなんで?
A lot.
いっぱいね
Belton, right?
ベルトンでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
This is it.
こうね
Yeah.
うん
Even if you can't see it, that much.
見えなくても、そんなに
why?
なんで?
You said it earlier.
さっき言ってましたね
why?
なんで?
I'll stand again.
また立っちゃう
Will this stand?
これ立っちゃう?
With 5D soap.
5Dソープで
Can be painted.
塗 れる
Wash it again.
また、洗いなさいね